we're in a technology
revolution. And many people
thought that the internet
was a technology revolution,
and to some extent
it was. But today,
instead of just one
major platform evolving, we
have five. So robotics,
energy storage, AI, blockchain
technology, and multi-omic sequencing
in the life science
space, which we believe
is the most profound
application of AI,
healthcare. And so this
boom, if you look
back at the railroad
boom, the amount of
investment that we saw
back then was about
6% of GDP at
its peak, 5% to
6%. The internet boom
was more like the
auto boom in the
early 1900s. It was
more in the 3%
to 4% of GDP
range. We believe this
five-platform innovation
strategy or boom is
going to move to
12% of GDP.
And we do believe
also that